<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lakeida Sprenkle</title>
    <description>I solve data problems and help business stakeholders get the answers they need.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 20:51:59 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 20:51:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>52 Weeks of Learning</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been looking for more challenges to keep my skills sharp and build new ones. So in addition to visualization challenges like Makeover Monday, I’ve been looking for one focused on learning key concepts in data science.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you can imagine my cheshire cat grin I was wearing when, while I was getting my daily dose of data science from &lt;a href=&quot;https://towardsdatascience.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Toward Data Science&lt;/a&gt;, I saw the perfect #52Week learning challenge to cut my teeth on. &lt;a href=&quot;https://towardsdatascience.com/a-complete-52-week-curriculum-to-become-a-data-scientist-in-2021-2b5fc77bd160&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;A Complete 52 Week Curriculum to Become a Data Scientist in 2021&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This curriculum is laid out really well. It’s essentially a set of curated resources grouped into weekly themes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Course Structure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Statistics and Probability (Week 1 to Week 6)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mathematics (Week 7 to 12)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;SQL (Week 13 to Week 21)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Python and Programming (Week 22 to Week 28)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pandas (Week 29 to Week 33)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visualizing Data (Week 34 to Week 35)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Data Exploration and Preparation (Week 36 to Week 39)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Machine Learning (Week 40 to Week 51)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Data Science Project (Week 52)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only thing missing is exercises or problems to reinforce the weeks concepts. So if you are looking for a fun, organized way to up your data science game, check it out.  And if you are doing it, please connect with me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://linkedin.com/in/lakeida-sprenkle-6ab7b12a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lakeidasprenkle&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, I would love to chat about our experiences with the material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;small&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Cover Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@gaellemarcel?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Gaelle Marcel&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/s/photos/weekly-learning?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/52-weeks-of-learning/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/52-weeks-of-learning/</guid>
        
        <category>Education</category>
        
        
        <category>Data Science</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Storytelling With Data</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://community.storytellingwithdata.com/challenges&quot;&gt;Storytelling with Data&lt;/a&gt; fam holds a monthly challenge where you can practice and apply data visualization and storytelling skills. Each month has a different topic, announced at the beginning of the month. Participants have the given month to find data, create and share their visual and related commentary. The challenge closes at the end of the month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I like most about this challenge, is that I get to use whatever dataset I want.  And if i’m being honest, there are times in some of the other challenges where I have a hard time getting motivated because I have no interest in the data or the questions it can answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you are looking for a fun, organized way to up your storytelling game, check it out.  And if you are doing it, please connect with me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://linkedin.com/in/lakeida-sprenkle-6ab7b12a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lakeidasprenkle&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, I would love to chat about our experiences with the material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Cover Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@dariuszsankowski?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Dariusz Sankowski&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/s/photos/writing?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/storytelling-with-data/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/storytelling-with-data/</guid>
        
        <category>Challenges</category>
        
        
        <category>Storytelling</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2021 Makeover Monday</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;New season (2021), 52 all new challenges to look forward to.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.makeovermonday.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Makeover Monday&lt;/a&gt; is a weekly challenge to work with a given data set and create better, more effective visualizations and help make information more accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My goal with this project is to use these challenges, where i’m working with varied datasets across different industries to force me out of my comfort zone and grow my skillset. I think it would also be a fun exercise to use other languages and tools. Tableau instead of Power BI. R instead of Python, even just trying out different packages, where applicable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you are looking for a fun, organized way to up your data visualization chops, check it out.  And if you are doing it, please connect with me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://linkedin.com/in/lakeida-sprenkle-6ab7b12a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lakeidasprenkle&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, I would love to chat about our experiences with the material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Cover Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@srd844?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Stephen Dawson&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/s/photos/visualization?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/makeover-monday-season-2021/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/makeover-monday-season-2021/</guid>
        
        <category>Challenges</category>
        
        
        <category>Makeover Monday</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boring with Highlights</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently attended a workshop, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.practicalreporting.com/practical-dashboards-detailed-course-description&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Practical Dashboards&lt;/a&gt;, it’s based on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.practicalreporting.com/about-nick-desbarats&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nick Desbarats’&lt;/a&gt; experiences designing dashboards for over 50 large organizations and teaching dashboard design to thousands of professionals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This course was eye-opening! He starts by having you watch a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.practicalreporting.com/blog/2019/10/23/practical-dashboards-video-now-available&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;presentation&lt;/a&gt; on why most dashboards fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The cliff notes version:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;because we need to understand what type of “Dashboard” our stakeholders really need.  He goes on to explain his taxonomy of dashboards and what they are best used for.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was able to quickly discern why some of my dashboards have failed.  And by failed, I mean the usage statistics are low. The stakeholders are just not using them anymore. Thats because what some of my users really needed, was a different type of dashboard. For example, they needed a type of Status Monitoring Dashboard, and what I provided was a Persuasion or Performance Monitoring Dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This course is a gold mine! I gained so much useful information.  Starting with first determining the type of dashboard needed, to focusing and restricting the level of information and metrics to the appropriate entity or role.  But there was one golden nugget that I mined and immediately was able to apply to current dashboards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the workshop, Nick talked about a design style he refers to as “Boring with Highlights”.  This means that in designing “Live Data” dashboards that you want to keep the overall palette neutral or subdued, so that when issues need to be flagged, they will stand out and will not have to fight for the users attention from other brightly colored design elements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This really resonated with me, because it made me think about my car’s dashboard.  I drive a Ford Flex and the dashboard background is black with white lights for the gauges. If everything is okay, then no other lights or icons are displayed.  This allows me to focus on what is important, driving the car.  But if, say my tire pressure is low, or it’s time for an oil change, thats when a colored icon will appear to grab my attention.  I’ve driven other vehicles that have several different colored icons all over the dashboard that are constantly displayed for you to view while driving.  I am immediately overwhelmed, as I can’t tell whats important; what’s not; Is everything ok? Should I take action?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I realized that with several of the dashboards I created, I had inadvertently created this same feeling for my stakeholders. Deep right? Told ya. And that’s just one insightful quip I picked up! There are so many more! Nick is dropping science son!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seriously head over to his site, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.practicalreporting.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;practicalreporting.com&lt;/a&gt; and check out his blog and videos!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;small&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Cover Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@alexrsu?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Alex Ramon&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/s/photos/dashboard-instrument-panel?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/boring-with-highlights/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/boring-with-highlights/</guid>
        
        <category>Visualization</category>
        
        <category>Dashboards</category>
        
        
        <category>Workshops</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Fake Data</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sonsofhierarchies.com/real-world-fake-data/&quot;&gt;Real World Fake Data&lt;/a&gt; is one of the new kids on the block, in the world of community visualization projects. The goal of the project is to build upon the amazing portfolio of Tableau Public vizzes, but with specific industries in mind to provide inspiration to those seeking a spark for their internal business developments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project is hosted by the people behind &lt;a href=&quot;https://sonsofhierarchies.com&quot;&gt;Sons of Hierarchies&lt;/a&gt;.  What speaks to me most about this project is that each of the challenges is based in real world business industries. So all the submissions are more applicable to real world business scenarios. That plus we also get two weeks for each challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you are looking for a fun, organized way to up your data visualization chops, check it out.  And if you are doing it, please connect with me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://linkedin.com/in/lakeida-sprenkle-6ab7b12a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lakeidasprenkle&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, I would love to chat about our experiences with the material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Cover Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@steinart?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Steinar Engeland&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/s/photos/fake?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/real-fake-data/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/real-fake-data/</guid>
        
        <category>Challenges</category>
        
        
        <category>Real Fake Data</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jupyter Notebooks</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This past Saturday I attended my first &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sqlsaturday.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;SQLSaturday&lt;/a&gt; event, hosted by the Portland, Oregon chapter.  Which also happened to be their first virtual SQLSaturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lots of wonderful presentations, across many topics, but one topic in particular really resonated with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sqlsaturday.com/1000/Sessions/Details/sid/105725&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Notebooks 101 for SQL People&lt;/a&gt; Speaker: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sqlsaturday.com/1000/Speakers/Details/name/julie-koesmarno/spid/401&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Julie Koesmarno&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
Are you a database developer, a DBA or a data analyst? Do you find spending quite a bit of time trying to reproduce analysis or reproduce issues and the troubleshooting techniques? This Notebooks 101 session is for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sqlsaturday.com/1000/Sessions/Details/sid/107611&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jupyter Notebooks for DBAs&lt;/a&gt; Speaker: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sqlsaturday.com/1000/Speakers/Details/name/rob-sewell/spid/2834&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rob Sewell&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
Jupyter Notebooks were once the realm of Data Scientists. New releases of Azure Data Studio, Visual Studio Code, and .NET interactive tooling have brought this tooling into the Operational team’s area. The biggest benefit of using Jupyter Notebooks is that you have your documentation, your code &lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt; your results in the same source controllable document.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently I use &lt;a href=&quot;https://happenapps.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Quiver&lt;/a&gt; to store my snippets and documentation on troubleshooting or adhoc queries. Prior to this, I was using apps like OneNote and Evernote.  Quiver has the same concept of cell blocks that you can add to the document. You can set the programming language on the code cells and it will provide syntax highlighting.  But what Quiver doesn’t have is actual code execution and a result snapshot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These two presentations triggered a lightbulb above my head, with ideas for notebooks flying around it, like birds swarming around a dizzy character’s head in cartoons.  This is not the first time I heard of Jupyter Notebooks, but having been the only SQL person in my company, since I started more than 7yrs ago, I only thought they were good for sharing scripts with the team.  And as a team of 1, didn’t see much point in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can’t wait to start converting my notes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;small&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Cover Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@fra99?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Francesca Tirico&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/s/photos/notebook?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/jupyter-notebooks/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/jupyter-notebooks/</guid>
        
        <category>SQL</category>
        
        <category>Jupyter</category>
        
        
        <category>SQLSaturday</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Had Happened Was...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Started out the year going strong.  Plans of participating in my first &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.makeovermonday.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Makeover Monday&lt;/a&gt; and completing and entire year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then 2020 happened…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’m faced with the decision.  Do I let this year win and continue to derail me from my tasks?  Or do I take back control?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You guessed it, taking back control. Starting with going back to participate in the weeks that I missed.  My plan is to start with the datasets and business questions that interest me most.  That should make it easier to build some momentum.  We are looking at 30+ weeks to make up for.  If I can get at least 50% of that, I’m gonna call it a win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;small&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@pavelanoshin?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Pavel Anoshin&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/s/photos/2020?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/What-had-happened-was/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/What-had-happened-was/</guid>
        
        <category>2020</category>
        
        <category>Inspirational</category>
        
        <category>Challenges</category>
        
        
        <category>Makeover Monday</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scheduled Refresh Can Disable Itself?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Whut… #skynet, #selfaware… Just stumbled upon a helpful tidbit of information. You all probably know this, but I must have been absent on that day when they covered it in class, lol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scheduled Refresh will turn off automatically after 4 consecutive refresh failures. So if anyone was like me and was puzzled why one of their schedules was disabled, this might be the culprit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/power-bi/refresh-troubleshooting-refresh-scenarios&quot; title=&quot;https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/power-bi/refresh-troubleshooting-refresh-scenarios&quot;&gt;https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/power-bi/refresh-troubleshooting-refresh-scenarios&lt;/a&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/scheduled-refresh-can-disable-itself/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/scheduled-refresh-can-disable-itself/</guid>
        
        <category>TIL</category>
        
        <category>PowerBI</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Could more Peace bring more Popularity?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Is it any wonder that nearly 1/3 of Generation Z and Millennials think other countries are better than the U.S., given the U.S. has been at war for more than half their lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;1117&quot; align=&quot;middle&quot; height=&quot;560&quot; src=&quot;https://app.powerbi.com/view?r=eyJrIjoiODE3YmYyMGQtNGFkYS00MWE1LTk4OGYtNmJmOGI5ODU0YWUzIiwidCI6IjFjNjkwYTIxLTBkNjQtNGY2MS1iYWY5LWI4NTNlMzA3NmQ2ZSIsImMiOjN9&amp;amp;pageName=ReportSection3b41768de5d00009bc9e&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;small&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cover Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@jacalynbeales?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Jacalyn Beales&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/s/photos/peace?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/makeover-monday-2020-week-06/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/makeover-monday-2020-week-06/</guid>
        
        <category>Political</category>
        
        <category>Murray</category>
        
        
        <category>Makeover Monday</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit 007, in favor of change or more control?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Are people in favor of leaving the EU, opposed to changing 007? This week’s Makeover Monday challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;1117&quot; height=&quot;560&quot; src=&quot;https://app.powerbi.com/view?r=eyJrIjoiZjFmN2M4YWMtNTM0NC00YWQ5LThkNzQtYTg2MzcwOTI4YzNkIiwidCI6IjFjNjkwYTIxLTBkNjQtNGY2MS1iYWY5LWI4NTNlMzA3NmQ2ZSIsImMiOjN9&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;small&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cover Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/@daguenther?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;David Guenther&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/s/photos/direction?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&quot;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/small&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/makeover-monday-2020-week-05/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/makeover-monday-2020-week-05/</guid>
        
        <category>Political</category>
        
        <category>Hutcheson</category>
        
        
        <category>Makeover Monday</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
